rude hard time
you hukum I'll cook him hmm short
you I believe they Jake I'll Pigface Ava
they told me the other day
right on
steep only four more
Oh be on my best behavior
try and stay on a single for once I'll
be on my best behavior
remember that time we stole the crown
jewels
all hail King Jameson folks the first
and Duke right what is your name anyways
me
[Music]
pretty serious too bad about these tools
we stole things miss that crowd
no kokum
I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in Troy
Wow did
nice mask
I'm sorry you're in your voice finally
quiet
about time you did something useful
someone finally shut him up